press-release-writing.com 2018-04-01

# eReleases - Privacy Statement

This privacy statement was last updated on November 29, 2004. MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) has created this privacy statement in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, www.ereleases.com and www.prfuel.com.

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba “eReleases”) abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. Upon reading this privacy statement, you will know:

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Web site.

2\. The organization collecting the information.

3\. How the information is used.

4\. With whom the information may be shared.

5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under MEK Enterprises LLC (dba “eReleases”)’s control.

7\. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) site coordinator by sending an email message to sales@ereleases.com or writing to us at the following address:

5024 Campbell Blvd., Suite D

Baltimore, MD 21236

To return to the MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) home page, please click here:  
[http://www.ereleases.com](http://www.ereleases.com/).

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) Privacy Statement

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) is the sole owner of the information it gathers on its site. MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) will only share your information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with Partners or law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our Web site. Demographic information collected from visitors to our website includes IP address, ISP, computer system used, browser used, and where the visitor originated (i.e., a search engine, website link, banner advertisement, etc.).

What Information is Collected and How it is Used?

* Free Newsletter Sign Up (PR Fuel newsletter)

We collect contact information such as first and last name, mailing address, email address, phone number, fax number, and company information such as company name and Web site URL. This information, which is stored on our third-party professional newsletter service, is used to send those who signed up a free newsletter as well as other special offers through email.

* Contact Us

We use email links as well as a contact form located on the “contact us” page and other areas of the site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission.

* Placing an Order

When you place an order on our website, you provide us with information that will be made public to the media and posted to online databases and Web sites. This information includes a press contact, which may include a first and last name, telephone number, fax number, address, email address, company name, and Web site. This information will also appear on each press release. The user also provides billing information, including first and last name, company name, email address, address, fax number, credit card number, expiration date, and acceptance of “Terms of Agreement”. This billing information is considered privileged and we strive not to share it with any third party. However, we will share billing information with our newswire partner PR Newswire upon request, including proof that “Terms of Agreement” were accepted. Upon request, we may also share it with our credit card processor and participating banks. If a member of the media is unable to reach the press contact, we may use billing information to assist the media, especially if a reporter or journalist is under deadline.

* Journalist Sign Up (to receive press releases)

We collect contact information such as first and last name, mailing address, email address, phone number, fax number, industry preferences, and company information such as company name, organization type, and Web site URL. This information, which is stored on our third-party professional newsletter service, is used to send journalists and those who sign up press releases as well as other special announcements through email.

Some MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) products are provided by MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) and a Partner. This Partner may not use your information for any purpose other than to contact you about the product or service.

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) will use any demographic data to learn more about the people and organizations that are interested in MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases)’s products and services to better target our marketing efforts. We may share aggregated demographic with outside parties to showcase the level of interest in MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases)’s products. No personal information will be shared.

Individuals, including previous customers, may also receive updates regarding the company’s products or services. If you opted-in to receive product updates or our free newsletter, MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) will use your email address and complete name to send the requested emails. To unsubscribe from these emails, see the Unsubscribe section in each email.

* Customer Satisfaction Survey

Customers’ contact information and any pertinent information, including comments, given to MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) can be used to create case studies and testimonials on the company’s products and services. MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) will use this information on the company’s website, as well as in marketing and promotional materials.

* Logged Files and Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site, as well as your behavior like if you completed an action or placed an order. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) uses cookies to identify which pages are being used and by whom. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) also uses cookies from relavant third-parties (including but not limited to Google, Google Analytics, Aweber, and Commission Junction) for purposes of tracking, measuring, and analyzing visitors and customers. These purposes include, but are not limited, to: advertising, affiliate/visitor tracking, ordering processes, marketing, conversion tracking, and split-testing.

This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses “cookies” to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

We will never knowingly allow any third party to use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Google will not link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information unless you explicitly submit identifying information via an interaction with our website or company, like completing a form, chat, etc.

Third Party Service Providers

MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) contracts with a third party to assist us in managing certain functions on our Web site, such as sending out our newsletters. MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) only provides third party service providers with the information necessary to carry out the service. Third party service providers are contractually prevented from using the information received from MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) for any purpose other than providing the intended service.

Links

The MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that these Web sites’ privacy policies may differ from those of MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases). We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any Web site you may visit.

Choices Regarding the Use of Your Information

How to Unsubscribe from MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) Email Publications

All newsletters and press releases emailed to subscribers include unsubscribe details. Any problems should be directed to:  
<http://ereleases.com/contact/>

How to Access and Update User Information

If you need to update your email address or any additional information, please contact MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) at  
<http://ereleases.com/contact/>

Security

Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority at MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases). We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. Once we receive your information that was entered into our web site, it is stored behind a firewall. All MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) employees are aware of our privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees who need it in order to perform their jobs.

Notification of Changes

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Web site, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.

Privacy Policy Compliance

If you feel that MEK Enterprises LLC (dba eReleases) has not complied with the policies outlined in this privacy statement please let us know at:  
<http://ereleases.com/contact/>
